<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyFavoriteCartoons</string>
    <string name="YuGiOh_Description">"Yu-Gi-Oh! It is a popular Japanese Anime and Manga created by Kazuki Takahashi. Mainly its story is the story of characters playing a kind of card game called Duel Monsters. Each player has a deck of cards containing Monster, Magic, and Trap cards, and the goal is to finish the opponent's Life Points and win the game (Duel). Each Monster card has a certain attack and defense points, and it is necessary to combine all three types of cards well to win the game. Of course, it was unthinkable that it would remain as an Anime, Manga or card game like every popular Anime, and it did. Games were released on many different platforms (PC, Game Boy/Color/Advance, Play Station etc.) and a movie was made. This movie increased their popularity and the number of fans increased rapidly.The new episodes of the still ongoing Anime series are broadcast on jojo tv in digiturk. Today, 224 episodes of Yu-Gi-Oh Duel Monsters aired and Yu-Gi-Oh Gx started, but this series is not even half of 224 episodes."</string>
    <string name="Bakugan_Description">It is produced by TMS Entertainment and Japan Vistec and directed by Mitsuo Hashimoto. It was shown on TV Tokyo in Japan in 2007. Nelvana Limited, on the other hand, produced the last episode as an English version, and after the series was completed, it premiered on the Teletoon channel in the same year. The English version was separated from the Japanese version after a while. A 52-episode series was created by combining 51 Japanese episodes and 1 English episode. The first season of the series premiered on Cartoon Network in the USA in February 2008. As for the subject, one day, cards begin to fall from the sky. In the beginning all children find it very entertaining. However, they soon learn that those Bakugans can talk to humans. Then their adventure begins when they learn where these cards come from."</string>
    <string name="Pokemon_Description">"Pokémon was created in 1995 by Satoshi Tajiri. The Pokémon Company, which manages the brand; Nintendo is a company founded in partnership with Game Freak and Creatures. The Concession is about \"Pokémon\" fictional animals that people called \"Pokémon trainers\" catch, train and fight for sport.\n"</string>
    <string name="Clone_Wars_Description">"Star Wars: Klon Savaşları, Dave Filoni'nin yönettiği ve George Lucas tarafından baş yapımcılığı yapılan bir 2008 animasyon filmidir. Hikaye her birinin Hutt Uzayı ticaret rotalarını kullanmak için Hutt Jabba'dan izin almak için uğraşan Galaktik Cumhuriyet ve Bağımsız Sistemler Konfederasyonu üzerine odaklanmaktadır."</string>
    <string name="Samurai_Jack_Description">Only Jack, his Mother, and the holy sword they were able to escape from the invasion escaped. But the mother and sons paths are separated, Jack has gone through a lot of training to fight the evil Aku. It is been 10–18 years. Jack is now ready to fight eternal evil."</string>
    <string name="Scooby_Doo_Description">"Summary. The big screen adaptation of the hit cartoon series Scooby Doo focuses on Scooby and Shaggy's lifelong friendship from the moment they met. After they meet, Scooby and Shaggy join forces with Fred, Velma and Daphne, who dream of becoming detectives, and soon form the famous Mystery Inc.\n"</string>
</resources>